// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is an invalid statement?",
    answer: "a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
    options: [
      "abc = 1000000",
      "a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
      "a,b,c = 1000, 2000, 3000",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is output of a=5 print(a)?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "a",
      "none",
      "=5"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Identify the type of datatype: &",
    answer: "logical AND",
    options: [
      "and",
      "&",
      "logical AND",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the output of x = 100 y = 50 print(x and y)?",
    answer: "50",
    options: [
      "True",
      "100",
      "False",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the output of print(2%6)?",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "ValueError",
      "0.33",
      "2",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "4 is 100 in binary and 11 is 1011. What is the output of the following bitwise operators? a = 4 b = 11 print(a | b, a >> 2)",
    answer: "15 1",
    options: [
      "15 1",
      "11 1",
      "25 2",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which one of the following have the highest precedence in the expression?",
    answer: "Parentheses",
    options: [
      "Exponential",
      "Parentheses",
      "Addition",
      "Subtraction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which one of these is floor division?",
    answer: "//",
    options: [
      "/",
      "%",
      "//",
      "///"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " What is the order of precedence in python? i) Parentheses, ii) Exponential, iii) Multiplication, iv) Division, v) Addition , vi) Subtraction",
    answer: "i,ii,iii,iv,v,vi",
    options: [
      "i,ii,iii,iv,v,vi",
      "ii,i,iii,iv,v,vi",
      "ii,i,iv,iii,v,vi",
      "i,ii,iii,iv,vi,v"
    ]
  },
  {
  
    numb: 10,
    question: "The expression int(x) implies that the variable x is converted to integer. State whether true or false",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "False",
      "None",
      "True",
      "cannot be determined"
    ]
  },

];